<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Getting started with Architexa">
   <intro>
      <description>
		 Welcome to the Class Diagram tutorial.
		 It will help you get started using Architexa's class diagram editor.
		 Let's get started!
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Opening a Class" >
      <description>
		 1. In the package explorer, right click on a class that contains some methods.<br/><br/>
		 2. Mouse over the <b>Open In Diagram</b> menu and select <b>Class Diagram.</b><br/><br/>
		 3. In the Class Diagram that opens, click on a class.<br/><br/>
		 4. Click the 'members' button that appears at the bottom of the class.<br/><br/>
		 5. From the menu, select a method to add to the diagram or select 'Show All', 
			which will add all of the listed members to the diagram.<br/> 
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Exploring a Class" >
      <description>
		 1. Click on a method that the class now contains.<br/><br/>
		 2. If no arrows appear, this method is not called by any method and makes no calls, so select another method.<br/>
		 3. Press the arrow on the left to see a list of all of the callers of this method.<br/><br/>
		 4. Press the arrow on the right to see a list of all of calls this method 
			makes, and select one of these methods to add it to the diagram.<br/><br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Expanding the diagram" >
      <description>
		 1. Click on a class in the diagram. Explore what classes it inherits from or what 
			classes subclass it by pressing the vertical arrows that appear at the top 
			and bottom of the class. (If no arrows appear, this class does not inherit 
			from any class in your workspace and has no subclasses).<br/><br/>
		 2. Try adding additional classes, methods, or packages to the diagram to explore 
			by dragging them into the diagram from the package explorer.<br/><br/>
		 3. Transition from your diagram to the java editor by double clicking on a class in the diagram.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>